VU THI PHUONG

Quang Trung, An Lao District, Hai Phong City | Mob: 0984 - 914 - 881 | Email: phuongduoc01@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Working professionally for a year as a Medical Representative with consistently being at the top of the sale chart. My main focus is on the best client-oriented service where teamwork, communication, persuasion, organizational skills highly excel at. I believe being diligence, open-minded and enthusiastic on the needs of customers just as much as mine brings the best experience to customers.

Career Goals

Being able to fulfill my working tasks well to contribute to the development of the company and carry out extra tasks to challenge myself in a less uncomfortable situations to develop my experiences and sharpen my skills. Seeing myself as one of the best medical representatives in 2 months and senior/manager position within 5 years.

Professional Experience

2017 - Current Zuellig Pharma Vietnam Co., Ltd.

Medical Representative

Working with

- Bach Mai Hospital
- National Otorhinolaryngology Hospital of Vietnam
- Hoe Nhai Hospital; Dong Do Hospital
- National Hospital of Obstetrics and Gynecology

Becoming the best seller of the 1st quarter with 163%

Feb 2017 NIPRO Pharma Vietnam Co., Ltd.

Internship

2015 - 2017 DOTRAN Vietnam LLC

Saleman

2013 - 2017 The 4th Asian Association of Schools of Pharmacy Deans Forum

The 13th Asian Conference on Clinical Pharmacy

Volunteer

Education and Awards

2012 - 2017 Haiphong University of Medicine and Pharmacy

BSc Pharmaceutics, Standard Program

Grade: Credit 7.67

2015 - 2016 NIPRO Pharma Vietnam Co., Ltd

Scholarship

06/2015 Haiphong University of Medicine and Pharmacy

Scholarship for Excellent student

Skills

Vietnamese	Competency	Internet/Email	
English	Management	Microsoft Office	
Communication	Teamwork		